[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "Do you think the world is a more peaceful place now than it was when you first became Dalai Lama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Dalai Lama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJR", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "Which one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "The younger one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "Really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "Do you ever feel temptation when you see a woman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Oh, yes, sometimes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Your Holiness, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Everything good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Everything good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "RB", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Everything healthy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Last now, almost seven years annually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "I got checked, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "Do you like being that famous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Celebrity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "I think it depends on one's own sort of matters of attitude towards this sort of -- some sort of popularity or some sort of good name.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "So you like famous people who are famous because they have done something serious, scientific?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Do you feel the world is a more peaceful place now than it was when you first became Dalai Lama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Dalai Lama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Do you think that is good for the world that they do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Yes, in principle, I support, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Do you think sometimes the politicians forget that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "I don't think generally politicians come from democratic country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "What do you think of modern China and how it's changed in the time that you've been Dalai Lama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Big change.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Dalai Lama"], "LOCATION": ["China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Are you pleased when you hear that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Did that offend you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBG", ",", "NN", ":", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Did you understand why he did that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Actually, he sent once sort of representing, something -- envoy or something, sent to me, explained the reason.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "You understood that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tibet"]}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Did he give you assurances that he is going to help you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "He inquired about Tibet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Does he share that vision?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Yes, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "What do you say to people who are thinking of doing the same thing and why are more people doing this now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "RBR", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "It seems - of course, it's extremely sad, very sad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "And what do you think it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "That's obvious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "But that is a big problem, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "I don't think, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBP", "NNS", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "RBR", "JJ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Do you believe that they are thinking the right way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Now, firstly, you see, they are -- they are sort of policies regarding their own people, now things, you see, there are indications, the seriousness -- see, these are indications they more moderate, more realistic thinking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "If the censorship -- if the censorship goes and the reality comes out, there is more chance of a deal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Certainly, 100 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "After this break.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "What does America mean to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Of course, the greatest modern country and I think a country, because of its democracy, the freedom, freedom of thought, freedom of speech, I think a lot of innovation, you see develop in this country.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "What do you think of what has happened to America and how can it get itself back on track again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Europe"]}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Is it a false dream, having a lot of money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "There is that, not only America, but also in Europe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Who are the most impressive world leaders you've ever met in your life who have that heart element in them, who understand it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "I think leaders have to act according to border sort of --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nelson Mandela"]}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ":", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "I mean, which people that you've ever met have really impressed you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WDT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "I think Nelson Mandela, I think what -- are one of the sort of quite impressive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJR", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Which one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "The younger one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "As a human being.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Not as president of America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 391, "question": "What did he say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "He couldn't --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Yes, right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Is that hard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Do you ever feel temptation when you see a woman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Oh, yes, sometimes see people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "ORGAN: Do you ever drink alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Have you ever smoked a cigarette?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Ever taken a drug?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "I don't know, I'm just asking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", ":", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Have you always been peaceful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Then, then -- wait, wait, wait.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Did you drink it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Then -- after my play, I return to my room, and there is the bottle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Do you watch television?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "What programs would you watch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Usually, like Discovery, and some sort of documentary film.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "Did you ever watch entertainment programs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 494, "question": "You never watched \"American Idol\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "``", "JJ", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "(Speaking in foreign language)", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Do you know who Simon Cowell is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Simon Cowell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Do you listen to music?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "No music at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "I have no interest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Do you ever watch movies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "You've never seen a movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "I saw movie, also the peace and war.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "War and Peace?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "War and Peace.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "And you've never seen one of his movies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Is he irritated that you've never seen one of his movies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Do you ever use a computer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Do you ever send an e-mail?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Have you ever used a cell phone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1959"]}, "docId": "120525pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "If I could replay one moment for you, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "I can literally, immediately after my final examination, that was 1959.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]